bwbconsulting.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy

## BWB CONSULTING LIMITED WEBSITE

###  PRIVACY POLICY

BWB Consulting Limited(registered number: 5265863) whose registered office is at Hine House, 25 Regent Street, Nottingham, Nottinghamshire, England NG1 5BS (“us” “we” “our”) is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to www.bwbconsulting.com (“Website”). Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. 

**By registering on this Websiteor emailing us through it** , you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy. 

##### INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU

When you visit or register on the Website you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name and contact details. We may also collect information about your usage of our Website as well as information about you from e-mails or letters you send to us.

##### USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

Your information will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of our Website and to supply the goods or services you have requested. We will also use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business.

In particular, we may use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the Website or our services. Further, where you have consented, we might also use your information to let you know about other products and services which we offer which may be of interest to you and we may contact you by post, telephone or fax, as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know.

##### DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

The information you provide to us will be held on our computers in the UK and may be accessed by or given to third parties who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes approved by you. Those parties process information and provide support services on our behalf. We may also pass aggregate information on the usage of our Website to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you.

Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent.

If our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners.

##### SECURITY AND DATA RETENTION

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

##### ACCESSING AND UPDATING

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us. We are entitled by law to charge a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

##### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the Website and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.

##### CONTACT

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to [Head Office](mailto:webmaster@bwb-consulting.com)
